<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<projects>
  <project>
    <position>Programmer</position>
    <title>Magic And Magnums Torch Edition</title>
    <description>A hands on game that uses a physical sandbox to model a terrain in real time for a tower defense style game to played on top of. Shown at a number of conferences and trade shows including GDC 2016.</description>
    <video width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RQ4DZulNDlM"/>
    <implemented>
      <task>
        I implemented the pathfinding of the characters in the game. The terrain and potential paths are weighted by steepness, height
        and terrain type to calculate an overall cost to travel the edge. A* is then used to calculate a path for each character.
      </task>
      <task>
        I also worked on the tower and character shooting mechanics. This uses a firing radius for each character type for general range,
        but also utilizes a line of sight calculation to see if terrain or other characters are blocking the firing path.
      </task>
    </implemented>
  </project>
  <project>
    <position>Programmer</position>
    <title>Don't Question It</title>
    <description>
      This project began as a 2.5D puzzle game created at a game jam and was then given to another group to continue working on.
      I was offered the chance to get the experience of working on a development team consisting of both artists and programmers
      before the rest of my class.
    </description>
    <implemented>
      <task>
        I implemented the fighting logic including wiring up the animations to the inputs as well as dynamic hit colliders.
      </task>
    </implemented>
    <links>
      <link type="play" path="~/UnityProjects/DontQuestionIt/index.html"/>
      <link type="source" path="https://github.com/TeamQuestionIt/FinalProject"/>
    </links>
  </project>
  <project>
    <position>Programmer / Technical Lead</position>
    <title>Gacha Town</title>
    <description>
      "Gachatown is a charming, colorful game that focuses on the experience of obtaining new characters from a gachapon machine.
      The fun doesn't stop there; with your collection, you can create an interactive town to earn you even more coins to extend your
      collection further! As you play, you can unlock more machines to build environments to your own preferences!"
    </description>
    <implemented>
      <task>
        I decided to use a SCRUM / Agile management style, so an overall roadmap was created and with that a one-week sprint task list was
        chosen. A complete, working (albeit crude) application was done by the one-week deadline and we iterated on that build, improving each week.
      </task>
      <task>
        My programming responsibilities were designing and implementing the collection and management backend systems as well as owning a main scene in the game (the town scene).
      </task>
    </implemented>
    <links>
      <link type="play" path="~/UnityProjects/DontQuestionIt/index.html"/>
      <link type="source" path="https://github.com/TeamQuestionIt/FinalProject"/>
    </links>
  </project>
</projects>
